Guide to the Goldie Krantz Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1950-1975; Series I; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  - Weissman, Arthur, 1973, undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Y (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Yedidia, Avram, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Z (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Unidentified, Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Research and Consultation, 1962-1975; Series II; 3' (7 boxes)
  The sections are in chronological order. The arrangement within each section is chronological except that financial records and other peripheral items are grouped at the end of the section.
  - Hawaii Dental Plan
    - Draft dental plan, correspondence, and clipping, 1962 January (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - ILWU-PMA Benefit Funds Contract Renewal
    - Community Medical Services, Inc.: correspondence and memoranda, 1965 April-August (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - "Memorandum of agreement between Pacific Maritime Association (for the Employers) and International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union…" and related memoranda, 1965 June (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound: correspondence and memoranda, 1965 May-July (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Kaiser Foundation Health Plan, Inc.: correspondence, memoranda, and contract, 1965 June-November (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Oregon Dental Health Foundation: correspondence and memoranda, 1965 June-1966 January (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - San Diego Health Association: correspondence and memoranda, 1965 June-1966 February (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - San Joaquin County, Foundation for Medical Care of: correspondence and memoranda, 1965 May-July (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Hospital Admission Study
    - Correspondence and draft proposals, 1966 Jun, 1966 December-1967 April (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Research Proposal, "Health Care in a Prepaid Group and Individual Practice", 1967 May (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1967 May-September (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Draft questionnaire, 1967 September (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Correspondence, 1967 October-1968 January (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Bureau of Social Science Research, Inc.: "Blue Cross Hospitalization Study: A Proposal", 1968 January 12 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Project site visit (Chicago): working papers, 1968 February 17 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Correspondence, 1968 February-April (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Health Services Foundation, Division of Research: "The Cost of Medical Care in a Prepaid Group and Individual Practice", 1968 April 23 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Correspondence, 1968 May (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Health Services Foundation, Division of Research: "A Study of the Medical Care Costs of Federal Employees Enrolled in a Pre-paid Group Practice and Blue Cross Blue Shield Plan", 1968 June 12 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Health Services Foundation, Division of Research: "A Study of the pattern of Medical Care of Federal Employees Enrolled in a pre-paid Group practice and Blue Cross-Blue Shield Plan", 1968 June 25 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1968 August-1969 January (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Draft Proposal, 1969 February 14 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1969 March (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Draft technical proposal, 1969 March 27 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1969 April (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Draft technical proposals, 1969 April (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Final draft technical proposal, 1969 September 3 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital: "Diagnostic Categories Selected for Utilization Review…", 1969 July 1 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1969 May-July (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Draft statements on "Physician Interview" and "Abstracting Hospital Medical Records", 1969 Jul, undated (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - "Administrative and Cost Proposal", 1969 September 5 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1969 September-November (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Resumés of participants, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Organizational chart, 1970 January 5 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - "Position Responsibilities", 1970 February 10 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1970 February-May (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - "Analytical Framework", 1970 May 25 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Correspondence, 1970 June (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Revised sample design, 1970 June 29 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Notes on meeting, 1970 July 7-8 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1970 July-August (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Revised sample designs, 1970 July-August (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Notes on meetings, 1970 August 27, September 23 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Draft household questionnaire, 1970 September (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1970 September-October (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Elaine H. El-Khawas, research analyst, Bureau of Social Science Research: draft, "G.H.A. and G.H.I.: An Analysis of the Impact of Organizational Differences on Health Care Utilization", 1970 November (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1970 November-1971 January (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Notes on meeting, 1971 January 13 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - "Data Specifications for FEHBPUS", 1971 January 29 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Draft household questionnaire, 1971 January (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Interview schedules, 1971 pre-March 1 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1971 February-April (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Pretest household questionnaires, 1971 April (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Hospital and physician services abstract forms, 1971 April (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Notes on meetings, 1971 April-May (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1971 May-August (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Plans of analysis, 1971 August 30 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Interview schedules and abstract forms, 1971 August 30 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Blue Cross and Blue Shield: "The Effect of Deductibles, Coinsurance and Copayment on Utilization of Health Care Services…", 1971 September 28 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1971 September-December (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Tables and related correspondence, 1971 October-November (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - Dummy tables for Phase I analysis, 1971 December (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - Notes on meeting, 1972 January 12 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - Interview schedules for Phase II, 1972 April (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - "First Data and Brief Analysis," Phase I, 1972 June (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - The Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies: research design for study of the Group Health Association, 1972 August (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Memorandum, "Protecting the Rights of GHA Respondents…", 1972 September 7 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Donald C. Riedel et al.: "Federal Employees Health Benefits Utilization Study," for presentation to the American Public Health Association annual meeting, 1972 November 14 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Bureau of Social Science Research: "Progress Report: Quarter Ending, December 31, 1972", 1973 January (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - Bureau of Social Science Research: "Progress Report: Quarter Ending, March 31, 1973", 1973 April (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Interview schedules and abstract forms, 1973 April (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - Bureau of Social Science Research: "Progress Report: Quarter Ending June 30, 1973", 1973 July (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Correspondence, 1973 July-1974 February (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - Donald C. Riedel et al.: "Federal Employees Health Benefits Program Utilization Study", 1973 July (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - Bureau of Social Science Research: "Progress Report: Quarter Ending, September 30, 1973", 1973 October (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1974 February-March (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - Bureau of Social Science Research: "Progress Report: Quarter Ending March 31, 1974", 1974 April (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Daniel C. Walden et al.: "The Use of a Panel Design in Survey Research…", 1974 June (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - Memoranda on data task force, 1974 November-December (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Phase I contract and related correspondence, 1970 June-1971 August (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Phase II contract and related correspondence, 1971 August-1973 September (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - Billing instructions, invoices, and related papers, 1969-1974 (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - "Statistical Models: Rationale and interpretation of Measures", undated (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Martin Marder: "Government Employees' Choice of Prepaid Health Plans", undated (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Miscellaneous code books, 1974, undated (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - Medical record abstract forms, undated (Box 8, Folder 157-158)
  - Mental Health Study
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 159-160)
    - Irving D. Goldberg et al.: drafts of report on pilot study, "Effect of a Short-Term Psychiatric Therapy Benefit on the Utilization of Medical Services in a Prepaid Group Practice Medical Program", 1969 August-1970 November (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - Manuals, 1971 December-1972 January (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Draft study proposals, 1972 Jan, March (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1972 January-June (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - Contract, 1972 June (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1972 August-December (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - Goldie Krantz: "Discussion of Findings Related to the Implementation of a Comprehensive Mental Health Service Program at Group Health Association, Inc. for its Entire Population with Possible Linkage to Area A Mental Health Center", 1972 December 30 (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 169-170)
    - Correspondence and related papers, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - Notes and draft contract, undated (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound
    - Correspondence, 1969 November-1970 March-July (Box 9, Folder 173-174)
    - Financial statements, 1970, undated (Box 9, Folder 175)
  - Advisory Committee on Dental Health
    - Working papers for meeting, 1971 April 20-21 (Box 9, Folder 176)
    - Working papers for meeting, 1971 April 20-21, 1971 July 22-23 (Box 9, Folder 177-178)
    - "Recommendations Regarding the Scope of Dental Benefits…", 1971 September 23 (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - Working papers, 1971 November 2-3 (Box 9, Folder 180)
    - Draft report, 1972 pre-November 21 (Box 9, Folder 181)
    - Report and Recommendations…, 1972 December (Box 10, Folder 182)
  - Medical Care Foundation of Sacramento
    - Correspondence, 1972 January-June (Box 10, Folder 183-184)
    - Draft proposal for health care for dependents of military personnel, 1972 June 23 (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - Correspondence, 1972 July-1973 (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - "Proposal…in Application to Become Identified as an Individual Practice Prepayment Plan", 1973 January 14 (Box 10, Folder 186)
    - "The Foundation Blue Cross Health Plan: A Pilot Project of Blue Cross of Northern California and the Foundation Community Health Plan", 1974 July 18 (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - Goldie Krantz: memorandum on the pilot project proposal, 1974 August 12 (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - Contracts, proposals, and statistical summaries, 1971-1974, undated (Box 10, Folder 188)
    - Publications, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 189)
  - American Public Health Association
    - Medical Care Section, Nominating Committee: correspondence and notes, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 190)
- Addresses and Publications, 1954-1972; Series III; 0.75; (2 boxes)
  The arrangement is chronological.
  - "ILWU Welfare Plans," sent to The Nation, 1954 November 5 (Box 11, Folder 191)
  - "ILWU-PMA Welfare Fund Pilot Dental Program," Southern California Dental Association Journal, 1954 December (Box 11, Folder 191)
  - "ILWU-PMA Program Extended," California State Dental Association Journal, 1955 November-December (Box 11, Folder 192)
  - "Why Prevention?," Alameda County Dental Society, 1956 March 3 (Box 11, Folder 192)
  - "ILWU-PMA Welfare Fund: Current Report," California State Dental Association Journal, 1956 September-October (Box 11, Folder 192)
  - "Consumer Experience in Group Dental Programs," American Journal of Public Health, 1957 January (Box 11, Folder 193)
  - "Consumer Goals in Prepaid Dentistry," California State Dental Association Journal, 1957 May-June (Box 11, Folder 194)
  - U.S. Public Health Service (with G. Krantz, consultant), The Dental Service Corporation: A New Approach to Dental Care, 1958 January (Box 11, Folder 195)
  - Speech on the ILWU-PMA dental care program, Washington State Dental Society, 1959 June 7 (Box 11, Folder 196)
  - U.S. Public Health Service (with G. Krantz on advisory committee), Speaking of Prepaid Dental Care: A Glossary of Terms, 1959 July (Box 11, Folder 197)
  - "The San Joaquin Foundation for Medical Care," American Public Health Association (Medical Care Section) and the Group Health Association of America, 1959 October 21 (Box 11, Folder 198)
  - "Prepayment in Dentistry," California State Dental Association Journal, 1959 October (Box 11, Folder 199)
  - "Welfare Funds and Dental Care," Washington State Dental Association Journal, 1959 December (Box 11, Folder 200)
  - "A Symposium on the Group Purchase of Dental Care: What Do Unions Want?," American Journal of Public Health, 1960 January (Box 11, Folder 201)
  - "Group Financing of Dental Care," Washington, D.C., District Dental Society, 1960 March 15 (Box 11, Folder 202)
  - "Report on ILWU-PMA Welfare Fund Dental Program," (California) Governor's Committee on Medical Aid and Health, 1960 April 21 (Box 11, Folder 202)
  - "Transcripts of Statements by Health Plan Organizations at Joint Meeting of Finance and Organization Task Forces, Governor's Committee on the Study of Medical Aid and Health", 1960 April 2, 21 (Box 11, Folder 203)
  - "Past, Present and Future of the ILWU-PMA Dental Care Program," Los Angeles Dental Society, 1960 April 25 (Box 11, Folder 204)
  - "Problem Areas in the Organization and Administration of Group Dental Programs," Prepaid Dental Care Conference sponsored by the University of California Extension South, 1960 April 29-30 (Box 11, Folder 205)
  - "The San Joaquin Foundation for Medical Care," American Journal of Public Health, 1961 January (Box 11, Folder 206)
  - "How to Choose a Doctor," Group Health Institute of Group Health Association of America, 1961 May 9 (Box 11, Folder 206)
  - "Labor-Management Welfare Funds' Views on Group Purchase of Dental Care," Michigan State Dental Association, 1961 September 17 (Box 11, Folder 207)
  - "The Indivisibility of Health Services: The Role of Welfare Plans in Rehabilitation," National Rehabilitation Conference, 1961 October 4 (Box 11, Folder 207)
  - "A Multiphasic Health Program," American Journal of Public Health, 1962 December (Box 11, Folder 208)
  - "A Consumer's Concept of the 'Image' of Dentistry," American College of Dentists, 1963 October 12 (Box 11, Folder 209)
  - "The Selection of Health Coverage for School Employees," American Public Health Association and American School Health Association, 1963 November 14 (Box 11, Folder 210)
  - "The Consumer Looks at Dental Prepayment," National Dental Health Conference, 1964 April 28 (Box 11, Folder 210)
  - "A Consumers Purchase of Medical Care through Organized Medicine," Foundations for Medical Care, Western Conference, 1964 June 27 (Box 12, Folder 211)
  - "The Effect of the Federal Program on Other Membership of Group Health Plans," American Public Health Association and Group Health Association of America, 1964 October 7 (Box 12, Folder 212)
  - "The Need for Utilization and Quality Control in Prepayment Programs," Massachusetts Dental Society Journal (Box 12, Folder 212)
  - "Psychiatric Need and a Demand in a Prepaid Group Practice Program," American Journal of Public Health, 1966 June (Box 12, Folder 213)
  - "The Dental Program- An Employer View", 1966 September 20 (Box 12, Folder 213)
  - "Medical Practice," American College of Hospital Administrators, 1967 March 7 (Box 12, Folder 213)
  - Irving D. Goldberg, G. Krantz, and Ben Z. Locke, "Effect of a Short-term Psychiatric Therapy Benefit on the Utilization of Medical Services in a Prepaid Group Practice Medical Program," Medical Care, 1970 September-October (Box 12, Folder 214)
  - "New Research Opportunities that Benefit the Entire Community," Conference on Community Centered Health Plans, 1971 September 9 (Box 12, Folder 215)
  - "Operational Experience" (with prepaid group practice), 1972 April 10 (Box 12, Folder 216)
- Teaching, 1959-1974; Series IV; 0.25; (1 box)
  - University of California, School of Dentistry: lecture notes, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 217)
  - University of California, School of Dentistry: research material, lecture notes, student handouts, and correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 13, Folder 218)
  - Howard University, College of Medicine, Department of Preventive Medicine and Public Health: research material, lecture notes, student handouts, and correspondence, 1963-1974 (Box 13, Folder 219)
- War Shipping Administration, 1941-1946; Series V; 5" (1 box)
  The series is arranged in this order: papers possibly written by Goldie Krantz, items of biographical interest, and miscellaneous papers related to the work of the Manning and Recruitment Organization.
  - [G. Krantz?]: memorandum on reconversion, 1945 May 21 (Box 14, Folder 220)
  - [G. Krantz?]: edited report on the recruitment and Manning Organization of the War Shipping Administration, 1946 post-August 21 (Box 14, Folder 221)
  - [G. Krantz?]: outline on the Recruiting and Manning Organization, undated (Box 14, Folder 222)
  - Scripts of radio broadcasts, 1945, undated (Box 14, Folder 223)
  - Job application, 1942 July 29 (Box 14, Folder 224)
  - Personnel records, 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 225)
  - Transcript of FBI interrogation, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 225)
  - Vouchers for travel expenses and related papers, 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 226)
  - G. Krantz: correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 14, Folder 227)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 14, Folder 228)
  - Applications for redress of grievances by Chinese seamen, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 229)
  - Maritime unions affiliated with the Congress of Industrial Organizations: "Wartime Shipping: A plan and a Memorandum", 1943 February (Box 14, Folder 230)
  - War Shipping Administration, Labor Agreements Division: "Comparative Analysis of the Rates of Earning and Conditions of Work of the Merchant Marine Personnel on Foreign Flag and United States Vessels", 1944 November (Box 14, Folder 231)
  - War Shipping Administration, Recruitment and Manning Organization: memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box 14, Folder 232)
  - War Shipping Administration, Committee on Crew Disciplinary Matters: Printed papers, 1945 June (Box 14, Folder 233)
  - National Maritime Union: Memoranda, 1945, undated (Box 14, Folder 234)
  - United States Maritime Commission: letter and memoranda, 1946, undated (Box 14, Folder 235)
- Biograhpy and Memorabilia, 1928-1977; Series VI; 0.75; (2 boxes)
  The arrangement is roughly chronological.
  - Roosevelt Junior High School: The Midget, 1928 November (Box 15, Folder 236)
  - Academic records, 1931-1936 (Box 15, Folder 237)
  - Professional correspondence, 1936, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 238)
  - Syllabuses, 1935-1939 (Box 15, Folder 239)
  - Class notes, [1936-1937?], [1939?] (Box 15, Folder 240-241)
  - G. Krantz: student essay, "I am a Communist…", [1939?] (Box 15, Folder 242)
  - Resumés, 1942-1975, undated (Box 15, Folder 243)
  - Political leaflets, 1953-1956, undated (Box 15, Folder 244)
  - Personal correspondence, 1953-1975 (Box 15, Folder 245)
  - Clippings on G. Krantz, 1954-1977 (Box 15, Folder 246)
  - Union membership cards, 1955-1959 (Box 15, Folder 247)
  - Certificates, 1957-1966 (Box 15, Folder 248)
  - Altrusa Club of San Francisco: correspondence, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 249)
  - Annotated clippings from medical journals, 1961, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 250)
  - Photographs, [1930s-1970s?] (Box 15, Folder 251)
  - Memorabilia, 1970-1971, undated (Box 15, Folder 252)
  - Date books and calendar, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 253)
  - Tape recording, "Oldster's Calendar", 1967 (Box 15, Folder 254)
  - Address book, undated (Box 15, Folder 255)
  - Elizabeth Condominium: correspondence, reports, newsletters, memoranda, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 256-262)
  - Elizabeth Condominium: correspondence, reports, newsletters, memoranda, undated (Box 16, Folder 263)
- Health Plan Publications, [1950-1975]; Series VII; 1' (3 boxes)
  The arrangement is alphabetical by the name of the organization publishing the material. Many items are undated.
  - AFL-CIO: "Employees' Welfare Plan" (Box 17, Folder 264)
  - Blue Cross Association: publications and clippings (Box 17, Folder 265)
  - Blue Shield: miscellaneous publications (Box 17, Folder 266)
  - C. U. & C. Health Services Society: brochure (Box 17, Folder 267)
  - Community Group Health Foundation: reports, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 268)
  - Community Health Association: miscellaneous publications (Box 17, Folder 269)
  - Community Health Foundation: clipping (Box 17, Folder 270)
  - District of Columbia, Department of Public Health: A Year of Health, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 271)
  - Greater East Bay Conference on Health and Welfare, 1954: working papers (Box 17, Folder 272)
  - Group Health Association: miscellaneous publications (Box 17, Folder 273)
  - Group Health Association of America: brochure (Box 17, Folder 274)
  - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound: annual reports, 1960-1965 (Box 17, Folder 275)
  - Group Health Dental Insurance, Inc.: brochure (Box 17, Folder 276)
  - Group Health Insurance, Inc.: miscellaneous publications (Box 17, Folder 277)
  - Harvard Community Health Plan: leaflets and clippings (Box 17, Folder 278)
  - Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York: miscellaneous publications (Box 17, Folder 279)
  - Henninger-Sandford-Fretz & Associates, Inc.: Professional Profile (Box 17, Folder 280)
  - International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union: miscellaneous pamphlets and leaflets (Box 17, Folder 281)
  - International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union: miscellaneous pamphlets and leaflets (Box 18, Folder 282)
  - International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union: officers' reports (Box 18, Folder 283)
  - ILWU-PMA Welfare Fund: miscellaneous publications (Box 18, Folder 284)
  - Jamaica Medical Group, Mental Health Center: progress report, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 285)
  - Kupat Holim: brochure (Box 18, Folder 286)
  - Leisure World: prospectus (Box 18, Folder 287)
  - National Opinion Research Center: "Public Attitudes toward Prepaid Dental Care Plans" (Box 18, Folder 288)
  - Pacific Maritime Association: annual reports, 1958-1963 (Box 18, Folder 289)
  - Pacific Maritime Association: annual reports, 1964-1970 (Box 19, Folder 290)
  - Prepaid group practice health care plans: synopses (Box 19, Folder 291)
  - Rhode Island Group Health Association, Inc.: booklet (Box 19, Folder 292)
  - St. Louis Labor Health Institute: annual reports, 1963-1972 (Box 19, Folder 293)
  - Teamsters Local 688, St. Louis: Health and Medical Camp (Box 19, Folder 294)
  - Union Health Service: miscellaneous publications (Box 19, Folder 295)
  - United Steelworkers of America: reports on benefits (Box 19, Folder 296)
  - Washington Clinic: leaflets (Box 19, Folder 297)
- Appendix
  These are the publications on subjects other than public health that were separated from the Goldie Krantz Papers and distributed to other departments of the Library.
  - Aptheker, Herbert. Negro Slave Revolts in the United States: 1526-1860. New York., 1939